Guide to the Richard W. Lyman, Provost of Stanford University, Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, 1959-1972
  - Foundations: Donner, Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Foundations: Esso, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Foundations: Ford, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Foundations: Luce, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Foundations: Mellon (The Andrew W.), Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Foundations: Nutrition Foundation, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Foundations: Rockefeller, Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Foundations: Sloan, Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Sloan Foundation AD12.10.4/204, Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Foundations: United States Steel, Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Foundations: Weyerhauser, Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Mid-Peninsula Free University 03.37, Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Frenchman's Hill Subdivision, Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Freshman Convocation, Undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Freshman English, Undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Freshman Pre-Registration Program, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Freshman Pre-Registration Program, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Freshman Seminar Program, Undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Fund Raising, Undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Funding Higher Education, Undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - -G- Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - "General", Undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - General Secretary's Office, Undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Gifts, Undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Goals and Objectives (University), Undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Government Relations, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Government Relations, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - State Government, California, Undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - United States Government, Undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Anti-Riot Provision (Public Law 90-132) Broyhill, Undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - AEC (Atomic Energy Commission), Undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Agency for International Development (U.S. Govt.), Undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Anti-Riot Clause Harvard, Undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Civil Rights (U.S. Govt.), Undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Copyright Policy (U.S. Govt.), Undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Defense Analysis, Institute for U.S. Govt., Undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Department of Defense (DoD) U.S. Govt., Undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Federal Funding, Undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Federal Research Support, Undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Federal Support of Universities (U.S. Govt.), Undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Fulbright Amendment (U.S. Govt.), Undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, Dept. of, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - HEFA U.S. Govt. Higher Education Facilities Act, Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Mansfield Amendment, Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - NASA U.S. Govt., Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - NDEA U.S. Govt. (National Defense Education Act), Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - National Institutes of Health NIH, Undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF), 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF), Undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - NSF Institutional Grant, Undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - United States Info. Agency, Undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Research Policy, Undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - U.S. Government - Task Force on Priorities in Higher Education, Undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Grade Point Average, Undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Graduate Student Assoc., Undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Graduate Studies, Undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Grass Roots, Undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Grievance Procedure, Undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Guggenheim Fellowship, Undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - -H- Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Haskins Laboratories, Undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - HEPL (High Energy Physics Laboratory), Undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Hester Report, Undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Hollingsworth, James E., Undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Honors Programs, Undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Hoover Institution, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Hoover Institution, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Housing: General, Undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Housing: Graduate, Undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Housing: Student, Undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Hukari (Suit), Undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Human Biology Proposal, Undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Human Problems, Institute for the Study of, Undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Human Relations Commission, Undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - -I- Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Industrial Affiliates Programs, Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Industrial Park (Stanford?), Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Innovation Fund Proposal, Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Insurance, Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - International Center, Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - International Studies: Faculty Appointments, Undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - International Studies: General, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Invitations, To 1970 August (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Invitations to Speak or Appear as Provost, Undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - -J- Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Journalism Proposal, Undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Judicial Council, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - SJ Council Prosecutor, Undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - -K- Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Ketchum, Jonathan, Undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Martin Luther King Memorial Fund, Undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - KZSU, Undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - -L- Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Land Development (SU), Undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Language Requirement, Undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Latin American Studies, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Latin American Studies, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Latin American Studies, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Leadership Conference, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Leadership Conference, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Leadership Development Program, Undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Legal Adviser to the President, Undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Libraries: General, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Libraries: General, To 1969 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Long Range Planning, Undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Lunar Scientist Institute, Undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - -M- Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Mancall proposal, Undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Mathematical Studies in Social Sciences, Institutes for (IMSSS), Undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Memorial Auditorium, Undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Memorial Church, Undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Metropolitan Studies, Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Mexican-American Student Confederation (MASC), Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Minorities (General), 1967-1970 June (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Minorities - Black Students, Undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Minorities - COGME, GSB, Undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Minority Employment, Undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Minority Enrollment, Undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Minorities--Fund Raising, Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Moses Proposal (Minorities), Undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Minorities "Racism and Prejudice" Course, Undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Minority Recruitment, Undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Minority Recruiment--Graduate, Undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Minority Group Staffing, Undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - "Talent Bank" (Minorities), Undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Minutes: President's Staff, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Minutes: President's Staff, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Minutes: President's Staff, 1966-1969 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Minutes: Provost's Staff, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Minutes: Provost's Staff, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Minutes: Provost's Staff, 1966-1968 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Modern Thought and Literature, Undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Moratorium, 1959 October 15-November (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Moscow University--Stanford Exchange, Undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Mudd, Seeley Educational Fund, Undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - N Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - NACUBO National Association of College and University Business Offices, Undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Nairobi College (E. Palo Alto), Undated (Box 7, Folder 26A)
  - National Bureau of Economic Research, Undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, Undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - National Foundation for the Endowment of Arts and Humanities, Undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Needs of Private Universities, Undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - News and Publications, Undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - -O- Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Oberlin College, Undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Ombudsman, Undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Open Campus, Undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - "Open" Meetings, Undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - "Opportunity Bank", Undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Organization of Universities, Undated (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Overseas Campuses: General, Undated (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Overseas Campuses: Austria, Undated (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Britain Campus, Undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - England, O.C., Undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - France, O.C., Undated (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Germany, O.C., Undated (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Italy, O.C., Undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Spain, O.C., Undated (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - P Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Packer Commission Report (Faculty Self-Discipline), Undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Pake's Group, Undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Palo Alto, City of, Undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Palo Alto Medical Clinic Contract, Undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Parents Day Program, 1967 October 7 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Parking Appeals Officer, Undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Parking Regulations, Undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Pass-Fail Option, Undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Patent Policy, Undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Personnel Department, Undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Ph.D. production, Undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - PHEAA (Pennsylvania Higher Education Assistance Agency), Undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Physical Plant, Undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Files from Pres. Pitzer's Office turned over to Provost's Office upon Pitzer's resignation; Administrative Candidates In-House, Undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Misc. Administration and Organizational Questions, Undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Board of Trustees, Undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Medicine, V.P., Undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - K.S. Pitzer--Files from desk, 1970 August (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - President Pitzer includes Pres. Pitzer's Speeches and Writing, Undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Planning Office and Procedures, Undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Police, Undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Policy on Campus Demonstrations, Undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Postdoctoral Education, Study of (NRC Study), Undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - "Princeton Plan", Undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Procedures, Undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Professorship-Hooker, Osgood, Undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Professorship: Sterling, Undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Provost's Office, Undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Provost's Office. Staff Assignments, Undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Public Broadcast Laboratory (PBL), Undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Public Events, Undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Public Policy Analysis, Institute for, Undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - "Publish or Perish", Undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Questionnaires, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Questionnaires, Undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - -R- Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - RAND Corporation, Undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Regional Medical Program, Undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Registrar's Office, Undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Religious Studies, Undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Research Administration, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Research Administration, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Basic Research, Undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Basic Science, Research Administration, Undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - "Conflict of Interest" Research Administration, Undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Indirect Costs, Undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Research Security Administration, Undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Research--Student Initiated, Undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Research and Teaching Assistants, Undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Type "C" Consultancy, Undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Unsponsored Research, Undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Research and Teaching Assistants, Undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Residence Halls, Undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Room and Board Rates, Undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - -S- Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Salary Information (Exchange), Undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Salary Review of 1967 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - San Francisco State, Undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Santa Clara County Board of Supervisors, Undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Security, Undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Selective Service, Undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Senior Fund Reception, 1968 April 15 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Serra House, Undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Seven Universities Group, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Sit-ins Other Universities, Undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - SPACE Miscellaneous File 1 of 2, Undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Animal Research Facility (Space), Undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Applied Physics (Space), Undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Art Building (SPACE), Undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Biological Sciences (Space), Undated (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Bookstore (Space), Undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Building 1 (SPACE), Undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Space: Building 10, Undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Buildings 100 and 110 (SPACE), Undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Space: Building 530/540, Undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Space: Building Security, Undated (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Business, Graduate School of (Space), Undated (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Space: Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences (CASBS), Undated (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Space: "Central Food Service", Undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Chemistry (Space), Undated (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Computer Science (Space), Undated (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - SPACE - Credit Union and Urban Coalition, Undated (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Space: Dermatology, Undated (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Donner (Space), Undated (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Dormitories (Space), Undated (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Earth Sciences, School of (Space), Undated (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Economics (Space), Undated (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Education, School of, (Space), Undated (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Space: SIDEC (Stanford International Development Education Center), Undated (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Encina Commons (Space), Undated (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Engineering, School of (Space), Undated (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Escondido (Space), Undated (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Facilities Planning (Space), Undated (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Food Research Institute (SPACE), Undated (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Fraternity Cluster #3, Undated (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Space: Graduate School of Business, Undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Hopkins Marine Station (Space), Undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Human Biology (Space), Undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Humanities and Sciences, School (Space), Undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - SPACE-Institute for Policy Analysis, Undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - International House (Space), Undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Space: "Jasper Ridge", Undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Junior Faculty Housing (Space), Undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Law, School of (Space), Undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Libraries (Space), Undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Main Library Development (Space), Undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Main Library Development (Space), 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Maples Pavilion (Space), Undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Medicine, School of (Space), Undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Memorial Church (Space), Undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Music (Space), Undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Operations Research (Space), Undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Overseas Campuses (Space, Undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Outdoor Primate Colony (SPACE), Undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Parking (SPACE), Undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Psychology (SPACE), Undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Quad Building (SPACE), Undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Radiation Therapy (SPACE), Undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - SPACE - Space Sciences Building, Undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Stanford Hospital (SPACE), Undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Student Health Center (SPACE), Undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Task Force on Planning Construction (SPACE), Undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Theatre Building (Space), Undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - SPACE - 600T - Trailer, Undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Tresidder (Space), Undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Undergraduate Dean (SPACE), Undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Sponsors, Undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Stanford-Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Stanford Associates, Undated (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Staff Benefits, Undated (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Stanford Cabinet, Undated (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Stanford-Cal Exchange Program, Undated (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Stanford Employees Association, Undated (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Stanford Facts, Undated (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Stanford Glee Club, Undated (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Stanford Hospital, Undated (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Stanford Housing Research Group, Undated (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Stanford Industrial Park Tenants, Undated (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Stanford-In-Mexico, Undated (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Stanford Linnear Accelerator Center, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Stanford Linnear Accelerator Center, 1967-1969 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Stanford Press, Undated (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Stanford Repertory Theater, Undated (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Stanford Research Institute, Undated (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Stanford Symbol and Motto, Undated (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - S.U.N. (Stanford University Now), Undated (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - SWOPSI - Stanford Workshops on Political and Social Issues, Undated (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Stanford Women's Liberation, Undated (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Stanford Voluntary Organization, Undated (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Stratton Group, Undated (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Students: General, Undated (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Students: Activities, Undated (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Students: "Activism", 1969 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Student Benefits, Undated (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Student Center, Undated (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - SCAN Students for Constructive Action, Undated (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Student Judicial Council, Undated (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Students: "Activism", 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Students for a Democratic Society, Undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Students: Social Regulations, Undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Study of Education at Stanford, Undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Summer Festivals, Undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Summer Session, Undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - -T- Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Taiwan Center, Undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Tax Reform, U.S. Government, Undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Teaching Assistantships, Undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - "Technology and Man", Undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Telecommunications Institute (Proposal for a Proposal), Undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Terman Faculty Planning Study, Undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Theater Building, Undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Tokyo University, Undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Travel, Undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Trebisnjica Project, Undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Tressider Union, Undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Tuition, Undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Tuition Benefit Plan, Undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - -U- Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Undergraduate Dean, Office of the, Undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Undergraduate Education Consortium, Undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - U.G. Programs (Social Policy), Undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Undergraduate Specials, Undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Undergraduate Studies, Undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - United Campus Christian Ministry, Undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - U.S.E. (United Stanford Employees), Undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - University Administration, Undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - University Governance, Undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - "Universities and Cities", Undated (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - University Counsel (President's Office), Undated (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - University Policies, Undated (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - University Policies-Use of Facilities, Undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - University Presidents Group, Undated (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - University Relations, Undated (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Universities Research Association URA, Undated (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Universities Space Research Association, Undated (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Urban Affairs, Undated (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Urban Coalition (Stanford Mid-Peninsula), Undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Urban Coalition, Undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Urban Studies, Undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Universities and Colleges, Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Brigham Young University, Undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Chicago, University of, Undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Columbia University, Undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Columbia Sit-in, Undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Cornell, Undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Denison University, Undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Harvard University, Undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Washington, University of, Undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Wesleyan University, Undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Yale University, Undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - -V- Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Vacation Policy and Schedules, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Vacations, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Values, Technology and Society Program, Undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Vandalism, Undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Venture Capital, Undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Violence, Undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Visiting Committee, Undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Visiting Scholars, Undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Visitors, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Visitors, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Visitors, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Visitors to Campus - Pompidou, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - -W- Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Washington Field Study, Undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Western Association of Schools and Colleges Accreditation, Undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Western Civilization, Undated (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Western College Association, Undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - WICHE Management Information Systems Program, Undated (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Winds of Freedom Foundation, Undated (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Wirth, Timothy, Undated (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Woodrow Wilson Fellowships, Undated (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Workers Action Caucus, Undated (Box 12, Folder 36A)
  - Writing Center Proposal, Undated (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - -Y- Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Youth Opportunity Program, Undated (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - -X- Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - -Z- Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Business School (Graduate), 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Business School (Graduate), 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Business School (Graduate), 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Earth Sciences, School of, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Earth Sciences, School of, 1964-1968 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Education, School of, 1968-1971 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Education, School of, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Education: Health Education, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Education: R and D Center, School of, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Education: R and D Center, School of, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Education: R and D Center, School of, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - School of Engineering. Minutes of Executive Committee Meetings, Undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Engineering, School of, 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Engineering, School of, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 14)